<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<bank xmlns="https://checkit.clontz.org" version="0.2">
    <title>Precalculus for Team-Based Inquiry Learning: PREVIEW Edition</title>
    <slug>tbil-precal</slug>
    <url>https://tbil.org</url>
    <outcomes>

        <outcome>
            <title>Linear Equations and Inequalities</title>
            <slug>EQ1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EQ/EQ1</path>
            <description>
                Solve a linear equation in one variable. Solve a linear inequality in one variable and express the solution graphically and using interval notation.

            </description>
        </outcome>

        <outcome>
            <title>Applications of Linear Equations</title>
            <slug>EQ2</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EQ/EQ2</path>
            <description>
                Solve application problems involving linear equations.
            </description>
        </outcome>   
        
        <outcome>
            <title>Distance and Midpoint</title>
            <slug>EQ3</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EQ/EQ3</path>
            <description>
                Given two points, determine the distance between them and the midpoint of the line segment connecting them.
            </description>
        </outcome>  

        <outcome>
            <title>Absolute Value Equations and Inequalities</title>
            <slug>EQ4</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EQ/EQ4</path>
            <description>
                Solve a linear equation involving an absolute value. Solve a linear inequality involving absolute values and express the answers graphically and using interval notation.
            </description>
        </outcome>

        <outcome>
            <title>Quadratic Equations</title>
            <slug>EQ5</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EQ/EQ5</path>
            <description>
                Solve quadratic equations using factoring, the square root property, completing the square, and the quadratic formula and express these answers in exact form.
            </description>
        </outcome>  

        <outcome>
            <title>Rational Equations</title>
            <slug>EQ6</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EQ/EQ6</path>
            <description>
                Solve a rational equation.
            </description>
        </outcome>  

        <outcome>
            <title>Quadratic and Rational Inequalities</title>
            <slug>EQ7</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EQ/EQ7</path>
            <description>
                Solve quadratic inequalities and express the solution graphically and with interval notation. Solve rational inequalities and express the solution graphically and using interval notation.
            </description>
        </outcome> 
        
        <outcome>
            <title>Introduction to Functions</title>
            <slug>FN1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/FN/FN1</path>
            <description>
                Determine if a relation, equation, or graph defines a function using the definition as well as the vertical line test.
            </description>
        </outcome> 


        <outcome>
            <title>Function Notation</title>
            <slug>FN2</slug>
            <path>outcomes/FN/FN2</path>
            <description>
                Use and interpret function notation to evaluate a function for a given input value and find a corresponding input value given an output value.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title>Characteristics of a Function’s Graph</title>
            <slug>FN3</slug>
            <path>outcomes/FN/FN3</path>
            <description>
                Use the graph of a function to find the domain and range in interval notation, the x- and y-intercepts, the maxima and minima, and where it is increasing and decreasing using interval notation.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title>Transformation of Functions</title>
            <slug>FN4</slug>
            <path>outcomes/FN/FN4</path>
            <description>
                Apply transformations including horizontal and vertical shifts, stretches, and reflections to a function. Express the result of these transformations graphically and algebraically.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title>Combining and Composing Functions</title>
            <slug>FN5</slug>
            <path>outcomes/FN/FN5</path>
            <description>
                Find the sum, difference, product, quotient, and composition of two or more functions and evaluate them.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title>Finding the Inverse Function</title>
            <slug>FN6</slug>
            <path>outcomes/FN/FN6</path>
            <description>
                Find the inverse of a one-to-one function.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title>Slope and Average Rate of Change  </title>
            <slug>LF1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/LF/LF1</path>
            <description>
                Determine the average rate of change of a given function over a given interval. Find the slope of a line.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title> Equations of Lines </title>
            <slug>LF2</slug>
            <path>outcomes/LF/LF2</path>
            <description>
                Determine an equation for a line when given two points on the line and when given the slope and one point on the line. Express these equations in slope-intercept or point-slope form and determine the slope and y-intercept of a line given an equation.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title> Graphs of Linear Equations </title>
            <slug>LF3</slug>
            <path>outcomes/LF/LF3</path>
            <description>
                Graph a line given its equation or some combination of characteristics, such as points on the graph, a table of values, the slope, or the intercepts.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title>Parallel and Perpendicular Lines  </title>
            <slug>LF4</slug>
            <path>outcomes/LF/LF4</path>
            <description>
                Use slope relationships to determine whether two lines are parallel or perpendicular, and find the equation of lines parallel or perpendicular to a given line through a given point.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title> Linear Models and Meanings </title>
            <slug>LF5</slug>
            <path>outcomes/LF/LF5</path>
            <description>
                Build linear models from verbal descriptions, and use the models to establish conclusions, including by contextualizing the meaning of slope and intercept parameters.

            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title> Systems of Linear Equations </title>
            <slug>LF6</slug>
            <path>outcomes/LF/LF6</path>
            <description>
                Solve a system of two linear equations in two variables.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title>Applications of Systems of Linear Equations  </title>
            <slug>LF7</slug>
            <path>outcomes/LF/LF7</path>
            <description>
                Solve questions involving applications of systems of equations.
            </description>
        </outcome> 

        <outcome>
            <title>Graphing Quadratic Functions</title>
            <slug>PR1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/PR/PR1</path>
            <description>
                Graph quadratic functions and identify their axis of symmetry, and maximum or minimum point.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        
        <outcome>
            <title>Quadratic Models and Meanings</title>
            <slug>PR2</slug>
            <path>outcomes/PR/PR2</path>
            <description>
                Use quadratic models to solve an application problem and establish conclusions.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        
        <outcome>
            <title>Graphs of Polynomial Functions</title>
            <slug>PR3</slug>
            <path>outcomes/PR/PR3</path>
            <description>
                Determine the zeros and their multiplicities of a polynomial in factored form. Describe and graph the behavior of a polynomial function at the intercepts and the ends.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        
        <outcome>
            <title>Polynomial Long Division</title>
            <slug>PR4</slug>
            <path>outcomes/PR/PR4</path>
            <description>
                Rewrite a rational function as a polynomial plus a proper rational function.
            </description>
        </outcome>
        
        <outcome>
            <title>Zeros of Polynomial Functions</title>
            <slug>PR5</slug>
            <path>outcomes/PR/PR5</path>
            <description>
                Determine the zeros of a polynomial function with real coefficients.

            </description>
        </outcome>
        
        <outcome>
            <title>Graphs of Rational Functions</title>
            <slug>PR6</slug>
            <path>outcomes/PR/PR6</path>
            <description>
                Find the domain and range, vertical and horizontal asymptotes, and intercepts of a rational function and use this information to sketch the graph.

            </description>
        </outcome>

        <outcome>
            <title>Introduction to Exponentials </title>
            <slug>EL1</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EL/EL1</path>
            <description>
                Determine if a given function is exponential. Find an equation of an exponential function. Evaluate exponential functions (including base <m>e</m>).

            </description>
        </outcome>

        <outcome>
            <title>Graphs of Exponential Functions</title>
            <slug>EL2</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EL/EL2</path>
            <description>
                Graph exponential functions and determine the domain, range, and asymptotes.
            </description>
        </outcome>

        <outcome>
            <title>Introduction to Logarithms </title>
            <slug>EL3</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EL/EL3</path>
            <description>
                Convert between exponential and logarithmic form. Evaluate a logarithmic function, including common and natural logarithms.

            </description>
        </outcome>

        <outcome>
            <title>Graphs of Logarithmic Functions </title>
            <slug>EL4</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EL/EL4</path>
            <description>
                Graph logarithmic functions and determine the domain, range, and asymptotes.

            </description>
        </outcome>

        <outcome>
            <title>Properties of Logarithms </title>
            <slug>EL5</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EL/EL5</path>
            <description>
                Use properties of logarithms to condense or expand logarithmic expressions.
            </description>
        </outcome>

        <outcome>
            <title>Solving Exponential and Logarithmic Equations </title>
            <slug>EL6</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EL/EL6</path>
            <description>
                Solve exponential and logarithmic equations.

            </description>
        </outcome>

        <outcome>
            <title>Applications of Exponential and Logarithmic Functions </title>
            <slug>EL7</slug>
            <path>outcomes/EL/EL7</path>
            <description>
                Solve application problems using exponential and logarithmic equations.

            </description>
        </outcome>
        
        
    </outcomes>
</bank>
